Genji is with
you staying out of trouble
Genji on my best behavior
Captain Genji how about a quick sparring
session you're on show me what you've
been working
on geni I heard you used to have all the
high scores here that's right wait
used to hey where did they all
go it's been a while brother my brother
is dead I killed him with my own
hands what's wrong Hanzo don't you
recognize me you may call yourself my
brother but you are not the Genji I
you so this is what has become of
you a Pity I will not be judged by are
you it is not too late to change your
course brother you are mistaken brother
I am beyond
Redemption together we could have built
an Empire that was your dream not
mine you will never amount to anything
we shall see
brother think you can do better than me
huh I am certain of
it what would have follow to think of
what we've become brother it's hard to
say who he'd been more disappointed by
any chocolates today brother those were
your amusements not
mine and I thought I'd taken my legs I
was a Reckless Youth but you are
something else
entirely you might be fast Genji but you
ain't faster than a bullet why don't we
find out
you seem well Genji I am a different man
now I am
whole I got you some chocolates Genji
Swiss they're the best thank you Angela
perhaps you could share them with
me Angela I have some chocolates for you
not Swiss I suppose it will have to do
thank you
gendi orisa you grow stronger each time
I see you my artificial intelligence
makes it possible to learn from my
experiences and from everything I
observe you wouldn't believe what I
learned about you Sparrow I am at peace
with who I was your threat does not
concern
me Genji ready for some sparring
practice of course you are the only one
I have trouble keeping up with
what is it like to have the chance to
change their past sometimes it doesn't
want to
change Kenji this is just like all times
our paths cross for now as to the future
we shall
see I always liked working with you
Winston no aore Small Talk always liked
working with you too you have a great
sense of humor
how do I trust a man who is half machine
the heart of a man still beats inside
me how can I convince you that I am
still a man I know what you are I'm only
sorry that you do
not it is good to fight alongside one of
my brightest pupils and you
master it is good to fight alongside one
of my brother lightest pupils that was
another
life does the suffering of the omnic
here trouble you master it does my
brother mandada gave much to improve
their lives but it was not to
be geni how was your reunion with your
brother he's still not ready for time to
flow forward
again I am victorious this time brother
mock death at your own
Peril I have the upper hand this time
master I will avenge you
brother
Master
Angela
Winston Bastion
catch back at you
brother H good aim McCree